ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials /4256
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Reprint numbers 604-674, 1989-1992. (Box 7)
  - Labor Historians and Immigrants: A Review Essay, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Technology as an Occasion for Structuring: Evidence from Observations of CT Scanner and the Social Order of Radiology Department, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - The Education Reform Movement and the Realities of Collective Bargaining, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - The Union Response to Employer-Initiated Drug Testing Programs, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Vocational and Academic Education in High School: Complements or Substitutes?, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Basu's Lemma and Goodness-of-Fit Tests, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - A Test of Goodness-of-Fit Based on Extreme Multinomial Cell Frequencies, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - On the Covariance Structure of Earnings and Hours Changes, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Effect of Wage Bargains on the Stock Market Value of the Firm, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Bayesian Quantile Plots and Statistical Inference for Nonlinear Models in the Two Sample Case with Incomplete Data, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Do People Make the Place? An Examination of the Attraction-Selection-Attrition Hypothesis, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Organizational Theories: Some Criteria for Evaluation, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Efficiency and Equity as Goals for Contemporary U.S. Immigration Policy, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Advancing Scientific Knowledge Through Participator Action Research, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Motivating Students to Study: Expectations, Rewards, Achievement, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Gender Differences in Current and Starting Salaries: The Role of Performance, College Major, and Job Title, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Union Participation in Japan: Do Western Theories Apply?, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Professionals and Workplace Control: Organizational and Demographic Models of Teacher Militancy, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - The Effects of Human Resource Management Decisions on Shareholder Value, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Does Performance-Based Managerial Compensation Affect Corporate Performance, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Is the Test Score Decline Responsible for the Productivity Growth Decline, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Scientific Illiteracy: Causes, Costs and Cures, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Interviewer: Assessments of Applicant "Fit": An Exploratory Investigation, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - The Productivity Consequences of What Is Learned in High School, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - AFDC and the Formation of Subfamilies, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Why the Apathy in American High School?, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Voluntary Turnover and Alternative Job Opportunities, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Work Processes, Role Conflict, and Role Overload: The Case of Nurses and Engineers in the Public Sector, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Employer Sanctions and the Question of Discrimination: The GAO Study in Perspective, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Organizational Differences in Managerial Compensation and Financial Performance, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Exit and Voice: Turnover and Military Intentions in Elementary and Secondary Schools, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - School District Leave Policies, Teacher Absenteeism, and Student Achievement, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Work-Home Conflict among Nurses and Engineers: Mediating the Impact of Role Stress on Burnout and Satisfaction at Work, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Personnel/Human Resources Management: A Political Influence Perspective, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Determinants and Consequences of Salary Negotiations by Male and Female MBA Graduates, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Cognitive Ability and Career Attainment: Moderating Effects of Early Career Success, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Worker Representation on Boards of Directors: A Study of Competing Roles, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Effects of Compensation Strategy on Job Pay Decisions, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Cultural Leadership in Organizations, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Immigration Reform and the Urban Labor Force, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Benefit Coverage and Employee Cost: Critical Factors in Explaining Compensation Satisfaction, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - The Importance of Recruitment in Job Choice: A Different Way of Looking, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - How Accurate Are Recent BLS Occupation Projections?, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Union Administration, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - New Directions in Labor Education, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Grievance Procedure Strength and Teacher Quits, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Why U.S. Students Need Incentives to Learn, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - On-the-Job Training of New Hires, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - The Worsening Shortage of College-Graduate Workers, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Is a Skills Shortage Coming?, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Effects of Work Values on Job Choice Decisions, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - The Flow of New Doctorates, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - The Current State of Performance Appraisal Research and Practice: Concerns, Directions, and Implications, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Perceived Equity, Motivation, and Final-Offer Arbitration in Major League Baseball, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Reprint numbers 675-700, 1993-1994. (Box 8)
  - Dimensions of Local Union Effectiveness, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Comparing Traditional and Integrative Learning Methods in Organizational Training Programs, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Diversity in Union Political Action: Implications for the 1992 House Elections (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Status Inconsistency in Organizations: From Social Hierarchy to Stress, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Social Context of Performance Evaluation Decisions, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Age Context of Performance-Evaluation Decisions, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Causal Models of Role Stressor Antecedents and Consequences: The Importance of Occupational Differences, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Validity of the Dimensions of the Pay Satisfaction Questionnaire: Evidence of Differential Prediction, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Does Affective Disposition Moderate the Relationship Between Job Satisfaction and Voluntary Turnover, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Effect of Dysfunctional Thought Processes on Subjective Well-Being and Job Satisfaction, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Asylum Policy and the New World Order, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - The Elusive Criterion of Fit in Human Resources Staffing Decisions, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Does the Targeted Jobs Tax Created Credit Jobs at Subsidized Firms, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Another Look at the Job Satisfaction- Life Satisfaction Relationship, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Recruiter Perceptions of Application Fit: Implications for Individual Career Preparation and Job Search Behavior, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Person-Organization Fi and the Theory of Work Adjustment: Implications for Satisfaction, Tenure and Career Success, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - A Policy-Capturing Approach to Individuals' Decision to Be Absent, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Subordinate Influence and the Performance Evaluation Process: Test of a Model, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Underinvestment in Employer Training: A Mandate to Spend, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - The Impact of Previous Training on Productivity and Wages, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - A Confirmatory Investigation of the Dimensionality of the Pay Satisfaction Questionnaire, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Responses to Increased External Support for Graduate Students, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - New Jewish Politics for an American Labor Leader: Sidney Hillman 1942-1946, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Schooling, Learning and Worker Productivity, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Promotional Materials. (Box 9)
  - ILR Press. N.d. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ILR Press. 1966.- Intro to Japanese Trade Unions+ Indust. Relations in Latin America, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ILR Press. 1967. Sensitivity Training (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - ILR Press. 1968.- Pamphlets about New ILR Books (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - ILR Press. 1969.- Book Order Advertisement (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - ILR Press. 1973. Incomes Policy: What Can We Learn from Europe (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - ILR Press. 1974. The Strike & Job Security inn the Public Sector (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - ILR Press. 1974. The Strike+ Job Security in the Public Sector (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - ILR Press. 1974. 142 Bibliography of Industrial Relation in the Railroad Industry (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - ILR Press. 1976. - Project Management An Annotated Bibliography- Advertisement (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - ILR Press. 1977. Documents Related to Arbitration + Book Publications (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - ILR Press. 1978. Mediation an Annotated Bib + Union Security in Public Employment (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - ILR Press. 1979. Order Forms Related to ILR Publications (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - ILR Press. 1979. Advertisements Related to ILR Publications (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - ILR Press. 1980.- ILR Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - ILR Press. 1981.- ILR Publications, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - ILR Press. 1982.Order Forms Related to Diff. ILR Books (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - ILR Press. 1983. Order Forms Related to ILR Books (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - ILR Press. 1984. Order Forms Related to ILR Books (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - ILR Press. 1985.- Order Forms Related to ILR Publications (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - ILR Press. 1986.- Order Forms Related to ILR Books (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - ILR Press. 1987. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - ILR Press. 1988. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - ILR Press. 1989. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - ILR Press. 1990. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - ILR Press. 1991. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - ILR Press. 1992. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ILR Press. 1993. (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - ILR Press. 1994. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - ILR Press. 1995. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - ILR Press. 196. Barbara Kingsolver Flyer, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 29)